-=THE LAST FANTASY=-荣誉出品 分享创作之乐 共赏字幕之美
-=TLF字幕组=-翻译: pig4869 番茄 校对: Felix_Zhang
片名: 恶魔的替身
喂
Hey.
你没怎么变 请坐
You haven't changed. Please, take a seat.
你妹妹最近怎么样啊?
How is your sister?
我有三个妹妹
I have three sisters.
胸大的那个 我一直想上的那个
The one with the big tits. The one I always wanted to fuck.
拉蒂夫 我听说
I hear the things, Latif.
你枪法不错
It says here you can shoot straight.
真是当军官的料啊 都已经是中尉了
Officer material, promoted already. Lieutenant.
自己拿根
Please, help yourself.
喝果汁不?
Juice?
拉蒂夫 我开门见山说吧
I won't keep you guessing, Latif.
你来为我工作吧
I want you to come and work for me.
- 为你工作? - 就在巴格达
- Work for you'? - Here, in Baghdad.
像是老朋友一样
Like old friends.
- 我们上学时就是朋友 对吧? - 是同学
- We were friends, weren't we, at school? - Classmates.
你不是画过我父亲的画像吗?
Didn't you once paint a picture of my father'?
- 你还留着? - 我给你了
- You still have it? - I gave it to you.
我告诉父亲是我画的 说起来真有些不好意思
I have an awful feeling I told him I did it myself.
知道这是谁吗?
Do you know who this is?
- 当然 - 错 错 错
- Of course. - No, no, no.
他可不是你想的那个人
It is not who you think it is.
他是法奥兹・阿尔艾玛里
His name is Faoaz al-Emari.
不是萨达姆 我天天见他
Not Saddam. I see him all of the time.
报纸上 杂志上 电视上到处都是
In the newspapers, in the magazines, on television.
我都分不清谁是谁
Even I cannot tell who is who.
拉蒂夫 这不足为奇
It is not so unusual, Latif.
斯大林有替身 还不止一个 伊朗国王也有
Stalin had a double. He had dozens. So did the Shah.
国家正处在战乱中
The country is at war.
我父亲不可能随时出现在 任何需要他的地方
My father cannot be expected to be everywhere at once.
大多数时候 人民期望见到他 而不是真的有什么大事
Half the time there is no good reason, but the people, they expect it.
况且一些该死的什叶派人渣
Add to that there is always the chance some fucked-up Shi'a scum
常常趁机暗杀他
will take a shot at him.
拉蒂夫 看看你
Look at yourself, Latif.
来来来 快看
Look. Look, look.
再看看我
Look at me.
我们像是双胞胎 是吧?
We could be twins, no?
你高些
You are taller.
高多少? 就这一点?
How much? This much?
别人不老说你像乌代・萨达姆・侯赛因吗?
Didn't they used to say you looked like Uday Saddam Hussain?
在学校不也是吗?
Didn't they used to say that at school?
拉蒂夫 我需要你
I want you, Latif.
我要你做我替身
I want you to be my fidai.
我要你当我兄弟
I want you to be my brother.
什么也别说了
Don't say anything.
给你十分钟
Take 10 minutes.
好好想想
Think it over.
我要是说不呢?
What happens if I say no?
就十分钟
Ten minutes.
他倔得跟茅坑的石头一样
He is shitting bricks.
他爷爷是个库尔德人 可惜啊
His grandfather was a Kurd. It's a pity.
但是他家早就搬到巴格达了
But the family's been in Baghdad a long time.
他父亲生意做得不错
His father's done well.
没记错的话 他是卖家用电器的
I believe he sells domestic appliances.
他从未反对过政党
He's never said a word against the party.
找了这么久 选了这么久 拉蒂夫最合适
Latif is the best we could find. And we looked.
我要定他了
Well, I have to have him.
你要什么有什么
You will have whatever you want.
我的就是你的
Everything I own will belong to you.
乌代
Uday,
我是我父亲的儿子
I am my father's son.
我会为伊拉克奉献我的生命
I would give my last drop of blood for Iraq.
可是战争一结束 我便会接手他的生意
But when this war is over, I'm going to work in his business.
我是长子
I am the eldest son.
我有兄弟姐妹 我也这样向他们承诺过
I have brothers and sisters. I have given them my word.
- 好好想想 - 乌代...
- Sleep on it. - Uday...
你是在要求我
You are asking me to
忘记自我
extinguish myself.
想好了?
Thought it over?
拉蒂夫 你要明白
Please be clear about this, Latif.
乌代选择了你 你是他的
Uday has chosen you. You belong to him.
五分钟时间 好好想想
You have about five minutes to think about this
否则 五分钟后 会有车开到 你阿尔阿德米耶区的家门口
before a car pulls up outside your house in AI-Adhamiya
而你所有的家人
and your family, every one of them,
你爸爸 妈妈 妹妹 弟弟
your father, your mother, your sisters and brothers,
都会被扔到阿布格莱布监狱
is thrown into Abu Ghraib.
主仁慈的话 他们会死得很快
God willing, they will die quickly.
我说得差不多了 还剩差不多两分钟
I've said too much. You have about two minutes left.
你有个专门厨师 四名仆人
You'll have a cook and four maids.
这些美女们也会满足你所有需求
These pretty girls will get you anything you feel like.
冬天的草莓 夏天的无花果 想要尽管说
Strawberries in winter, figs in July. Just ask me.
但是你要是未经允许 敢碰她们中任何一个
But lay a finger on one of them without prior permission
你就别想再站着出去
and you'll never walk upright again.
这些是乌代的房间
And these are Uday's rooms.
既然你就要是他兄弟了 他让你住这里
He wants you to use them, now that you are to be his brother.
真皮沙发 意大利大理石地板 都是詹弗兰克・简耐里设计的
Leather sofas, Italian marble, all designed by Gianfranco Giannelli.
定制的鞋子 定制的西装
Handmade shoes, suits,
布莱奥尼 范思哲 阿玛尼 当然
Brioni, Versace, Armani, of course.
有还真丝领带 百年灵 卡地亚和劳力士手表
Silk ties, watches. Breitling, Cartier, Rolex.
真丝睡衣
Silk pajamas.
这些都是上乘品
These are very nice.
这可怜的孩子整天发愁怎么穿
Poor child never knows what to wear.
他一会儿一个想法
He changes his mind every five minutes.
衣服还要和他的车子搭配
Depends on what car he's driving.
老实说 亲爱的 这孩子快把我弄疯了
Honestly, habibi, that boy, he wears me out.
你该拾掇下自己了
You should probably clean yourself up.
不能打电话
No calls.
接电话行 打电话不行
Incoming, yes. Outgoing, no.
我是穆内姆・汉姆德・阿尔缇克里缇
My name is Munem Hammed al-Tikriti.
我们会时常见面的
We're going to be seeing a lot of each other.
我每周都给我母亲写信
I write to my mother once a week.
她会认为我在伊朗出事了
She's going to think that I got killed in Iran.
听天由命吧
Inshallah.
听天由命?
Inshallah?
我家里会认为我死了
My family are going to think that I'm dead.
就让他们以为你牺牲了
Let them think you died a martyr.
我想这很难 但是乌代希望这样
I know it's difficult, but it's what Uday wants.
别无他法
He will accept nothing less.
我母亲会找遍巴格达所有医院
She will be knocking on the door of every hospital in Baghdad.
你今天晚上祈祷时
When you say your prayers tonight,
关上灯睡觉时
when you tum out the light and close your eyes,
应该这样对自己说
this is what you should be saying to yourself,
『拉蒂夫死了 他在伊朗牺牲了
"Latif Yahia is dead. He died in Iran.
希望真主宽恕他
"May God have mercy on him.
我现在是乌代・萨达姆・侯赛因』
"Now I am Uday Saddam Hussein."
你好
Guten Tag.
请把衣服脱了
Take off your clothes, please.
咳嗽下
Cough.
再咳下
One more time.
再来一下
And one more time, please.
乌代比他高三厘米
Uday is three centimeters taller.
穿增高鞋就行
We can use built-up shoes.
快看 他真不错啊
Look at that. He is perfect.
- 乌代 无聊死了 - 闭嘴
- Uday, this is boring. - Shut up.
你怎么能整晚坐在这里看自己
How can you sit here all night looking at yourself?
- 他看起来很不错 - 他一点都不像你
- He looks great. - He doesn't even look like you.
什么?
What?
他那个太大了
His cock's too big.
什么叫他那个太大?
What do you mean, his cock is too big?
乌代的生活 了解下
Uday's life story. Learn it.
快 快告诉我
Come on, come on, tell me.
脸型 发型 鼻子 体型相似度 在九十分以上
Shape of face, hair, nose, physique, all in the high 90s.
- 很好 - 你眼睛比他大五毫米
- Good. - Your eyes are five millimeters bigger.
- 这个他们可以给他整个容 - 牙呢? 牙怎么弄?
- They can use make-up. - And the teeth? What about the teeth?
咱们真是一个模子刻出来的啊
Two peas in a pod.
- 我刚才正试牙套 - 微笑 保持住 微笑
- I was just trying the teeth. - Smile. Go on, smile.
不 不 不 像这样
No, no, no. Like this.
发型改一改
And do the hair. Do the hair.
你喜欢劳力士
You like the Rolex.
送你了
Keep it.
你穿蓝色很好看
You look good in blue.
嗯 这很适合你
Yes, it definitely suits you.
拉蒂夫 快点
Latif hurry up.
- 冰太多了 - 我是不是可以说蓝色是你的风格
- There's too much ice. - Can I say blue is your color?
闭嘴
Shut up.
我喜欢你打拳的方式
I like the way you fight.
你打斗时候和我很像
You fight like me.
他打斗的时候很像我
He fights like me.
我和林兹医生谈过了
I had a word with Dr. Linz.
他说你那个太大了
He says your cock's too big.
得做个消减手术
We need to make a surgical reduction.
- 做什么? - 切除一小段
- A what? - Chop a bit off.
- 什么? - 不会太多
- What? - Not much.
就一点点
Just a teeny-weeny.
就一点点?
Not much?
巴格达的女人们都知道我那个的大小
My cock is well-known in Baghdad. The women, they talk.
我跟你开玩笑的 你傻啊
I'm joking with you, you fuck.
这是赛德・卡姆讷
This is Said Kammuneh.
伊拉克奥委会委员
He's a member of the Iraqi Olympic Committee.
他要给你看些东西
He has something to show you.
这是乌代・萨达姆・侯赛因 个人收藏中的一件
This is from the personal collection of Uday Saddam Hussain.
那个人 他是个警察
That guy, he was a police officer.
我们过去是一个球队的
We were on the same football team.
左脚技术很厉害 头球很出色
Great left foot. Good in the air.
这下是我打的 等下
I shot this myself. Wait a minute.
不错吧?
Good work, huh?
我们从东德和俄罗斯人那儿学到不少手段
We got a lot of this shit from the East Germans and the Russians.
看见那个人没? 那是摔跤运动员拉科提
See that guy'? That's Rakti, the wrestler.
在莫斯科拿过铜牌
He won a bronze medal in Moscow.
总统称他是共和国的利剑
The President calls him the sharp sword of the Republic.
你知道海法大街上挨着路灯的加油站吧?
You know that gas station on Haifa Street by the lights?
总统把它赠给这个人了
The President gave him that.
这死胖子一月能挣两万块
The fat fuck's making 20 grand a month.
数目不小啊
That's good money.
剩下的你自己看
Look, I'll leave this with you.
- 看够没? - 够没?
- Seen enough? - Enough?
你问我看得够不够?
Have I seen enough?
我记得萨达姆・侯赛因就职的那天
I remember the day Saddam Hussein became president of this country.
我就穿着小短裤 大喊着跑过一条条大街
I was still in short trousers. We ran through the streets, shouting,
『萨达姆! 萨达姆・侯赛因! 萨达姆・侯赛因! 』 我们还朝天开枪以示庆祝
"Saddam! Saddam Hussain! Saddam Hussein!" Firing our guns.
连我的父亲 甚至连我的父亲
Even my father. Even my father.
这东西 穆饶...
This stuff, Munem...
这些人 赛德应该先解释一下
These people". I hope Said said something about this.
他们是罪犯 是被人遗弃的人
They're criminals, deserters.
就是强奸犯 诈骗犯 杀人犯
Pornographers, counterfeiters, murderers, of course.
叛国者 他们是共和国的敌人
Putschists. Enemies of the Republic.
你别忘了 是萨达姆・侯赛因建立了这个国家
Saddam Hussein built this country. Never forget that.
学校 公路 医院 清真寺
The schools, the roads, hospitals, the mosques.
他给予伊拉克人民一切他们所需要的
He gave the Iraqi people everything they want.
他要求的回报就一点
He demands only one thing in return.
永远不要反对他的家族
Never raise a hand against his family.
谁这样做 谁就将受到惩罚
Do so and you will suffer.
他爱的人也将受到惩罚
The people you love will suffer.
用心干 你会成为这个家庭的一员
Do well here, work hard and you'll be one of the family.
总有一天这一切会结束的 顺其自然吧
One day all this will be over. Inshallah.
顺其自然?
Inshallah?
只有真主知道是什么时候
Only God knows when.
来来来 快过来
Come, come, come, come, come.
穆饶凡桓咝肆 你看他
Munem disapproves. Look at him.
他生我气了 他觉得我该把你放家里
He's angry with me. He thinks I should leave you at home.
- 这是谁? - 拉蒂夫? 他是我兄弟
- Who's this? - Latif'? He's my brother.
没人知道萨达姆有三个儿子
Nobody must know this, but Saddam, he has three sons.
你敢告诉任何人
You tell anybody this,
我就会用刀割下你的舌头去喂猫
I will have to out your tongue out with a razor and feed it to the cat.
我的就是他的
Everything I own, I give to him.
我不是你的
You don't own me.
萨拉布 贝鲁特最正的妞
Sarrab, best fuck in Beirut.
我来为你松松领带
Loosen your tie. Let me do it for you.
好了 舒服多了 是吧?
There. Isn't that better?
说话小心点
Ba careful what you say.
我能看穿你心思
I can read your mind.
你真是总统的儿子?
Are you really the President's son?
你知道电视上怎么说的
You know what they say on TV.
我们都是总统的孩子
We are all the President's sons.
喂!
Hey!
嗨
你看他
Look at him.
他舍不得把手从那人妖身上拿下来
He can't keep his hands off that drag queen.
可怜的乌代
Poor Uday.
有时我觉得他想折腾死自己
Sometimes I think he wants to fuck himself to death.
不好意思 失陪下
Will you excuse me a moment?
钥匙
Keys.
给我钥匙
Give me the keys.
该死的 把钥匙给我
Give me the fucking keys!
宝贝 我爱死你的奶子了!
Baby, I so love your tits!
亲爱的 但愿如此 你付钱了的
I hope so, lover. You paid for them.
你对我兄弟干什么了?
What have you done with my brother?
你看 穆饶?
You see, Munem?
纪律 我们必须得有纪律
Discipline. We must have discipline.
没有纪律 就没有秩序
If we do not have discipline, we have no control.
没有秩序就会混乱
If we have no control, we have chaos.
混乱后紧接着就会有骚动
If we have chaos, we have disorder.
你知道 是吧 拉蒂夫? 这道理很简单
You do understand, Latif? It is quite simple.
我们必须要有纪律
We must have discipline.
明白没有?
Got it?
好
Good.
拉蒂夫 给你五分钟
Latif. Five minutes.
拉蒂夫
Latif.
- 不 不 不行! - 我们必须要有纪律
- No, no, no! - We must have discipline!
纪律 必须有纪律
Discipline! We must have discipline!
刚才怎么样 穆饶?
How was that, Munem?
棒极了
Excellent.
对不起
Sorry.
很好
Good.
掏空口袋
Empty your pockets.
我爷爷
My grandfather,
他和我说话还像对待小孩
he talks to me the same way he did when I was 10 years old.
真主真是伟大
God is great.
他赐予我两个儿子
He gave me two sons.
现在我有了三个了
Now I have three.
管好自己的言行 别让我抓住任何把柄
Make sure you give me no reason to be angry with you.
怎么样?
And?
乌代 你欠我五十第纳尔
Uday, you owe me 50 dinar.
五十第纳尔?
50 dinar?
瞧见没?
You see?
你哥哥真是个铁公鸡 从他这拿走一个子都难
Trying to get money from your brother is like trying to get blood from a stone.
什么?
What?
那不是乌代
It's not him.
什么?
What?
该你了 兄弟
It's your turn, brother.
妈的 该死的科威特人
Fuck them. Fucking Kuwaitis.
我恨死他们了
I hate them all.
猪狗不如
Worse than horseflies.
兄弟们 欢迎来到巴格达
My brothers, welcome to Baghdad.
妈的!
Fuck!
妈的! 妈的! 妈的! 妈的!
Fuck! Fuck, fuck, fuck!
该死的科威特人
Fucking Kuwaitis!
我恨犹太人 我恨科威特人
I fucking hate Jews, I hate horseflies
我恨波斯人
and I hate fucking Persians,
但我最恨科威特人
but I hate fucking Kuwaitis more!
他们侮辱我们
They insult us.
这些下流坯子 竟然强暴我们的女人
They are filth. They maul our women.
科威特人每年榨取我们两亿八千万美元
The Kuwaitis have been stealing $280 million a year
就从鲁迈拉的油田
from the oilfields at Rumaila.
每年榨取两亿八千万美元!
$280 million a year!
我们正调查的那些武器
You know we traced the weapon.
我刚刚得知幕后黑手就是该死的科威特
I just know the fucking Kuwaitis are behind this!
希望父亲能把他们灭了
I hope my father wipes them out.
告诉你们 我不怕有人听到
No, I'm telling you this. I don't care who knows it!
酋长的时代结束了 结束了!
The age of the sheikhs is over. Over!
- 什么事? - 是我 亲爱的
- What? - It's me, habibi.
你干什么呢?
What are you doing right now?
我在修指甲 把它们修得又尖又美
I'm getting my nails done. Nice and sharp.
这样更适合挠你
The better to scratch you with.
我说过我很喜欢你屁股吧?
Did I ever tell you how much I love your ass?
你屁股是我在巴格达见过的最性感的 一会见
It's the best ass in Baghdad. I'll see you soon.
喂 你 说你呢!
Hey, you, you!
你会见到很多美女
You'll meet many women.
妓女 埃曼苏尔的贵妇们
Whores, wealthy women from Al Mansour
她们来寻求帮助 你也相应得到乐子
who come looking for a favor and offer you favors in return.
还有乌代从大街上抓来的女学生
Schoolgirls he snatches off the street.
- 你会享受到的你应得的 - 准备好没 伙计?
- You'll be given your fair share. - Ready, guys?
坚决不能跟乌代选中的女人说话
Never even speak to a woman Uday has chosen for himself.
他疯了
He is insane.
你知道的 穆饶
You know it, Munem.
他疯了
He's insane.
你没办法 只能视若罔闻
You turn a blind eye. You have no choice.
我明白
I understand that.
你是个好人 选错了工作
You are a good man in a bad job.
你看他
Look at him.
他是个疯子
He's psychotic.
来 再亲下 多亲几下
Come on, kiss. Kiss more. More. Kiss, kiss.
谁今天晚上想陪我啊? 你?
Who wants to sleep with me tonight? You?
在一名英国工人公寓的窗外
Through the window of a British worker's flat,
科威特战争正在进行
the Battle of Kuwait unfolds.
萨达姆・侯赛因 非常简单 你不该欺负你的邻国
Saddam Hussein, very simply, you cannot bully your neighbor
你不该企图消灭 一个阿拉伯联盟的成员国
You cannot wipe him out, a member of the Arab League,
一个联合国成员国
a member of the United Nations.
萨达姆・侯赛因! 阿尔卡迪西亚会战的英雄
Saddam Hussein! The hero of the Battle of Qadisiyyah.
阿拉伯国家的骑士
The knight of the Arab nations.
先知的直系后裔
Direct descendant of the prophet.
萨拉姆 高贵的战士
Saddam the noble fighter.
阿尔侯赛因阿訇的子孙
Scion of the family of Imam al-Hussein.
女士们 先生们 有请乌代・萨达姆・侯赛因
Ladies and gentlemen, Uday Saddam Hussain.
酋长的时代已经结束!
The age of the sheikhs is over!
真主万能 在他的帮助下
With the help of Almighty God,
科威特回归祖国了
Kuwait has come home!
喂 你 戴牙套的那个
Hey, you. The teeth. You with the teeth.
过来 我载你一程
Come on. I'll give you a ride.
嗨! 嗨嗨嗨! 你! 不不不不 你 你 就是你
Hey! Hey, hey, hey! You! NO, no, no, no. You, you, you.
喂 说你呢
Hey, you.
别害怕 来 我载你一程
Don't be scared. Come for a ride.
过来 上车 我送你回家
Come on, get in the car. I'll give you a lift home.
我会送你回去
I'll take you back.
喂 别害怕 你跑什么啊 你跑什么?
Hey, don't be scared. Why do you run'? Why do you run?
过来啊 你跑什么啊? 我送你回家
Come on. Why are you running? I'll take you home.
来吧
Come on.
喂 你来不来?
Hey. How about you?
我喜欢你的发型
I love what you've done with your hair.
喂 喂 喂!
Hey, hey, hey!
没事 没事 别害怕 别害怕
It's okay, it's okay. Don't be scared. Don't be scared.
没事的
It's all right.
你真漂亮 别害怕 我不会伤害你的
You're beautiful. Don't be scared. I'm not going to hurt you.
兄弟 他很漂亮 想要她不?
Brother, she's beautiful. You want her?
- 带走 - 不要!
- Take. - No!
怎么了? 怎么了? 别他妈的那样看我
What? What? Don't fucking look at me like that.
- 怎样看你? - 就刚才那样
- Like what? - Like that.
我知道这个表情 我知道你在想什么
I know that fucking look. I know what you're thinking.
想想你喜欢些什么 我就是喜欢女人 我就是喜欢女人
Think what the fuck you like. I like cunt. I want cunt.
看到女人 我就想上 那又怎样
I see a cunt, I want to fuck it. I don't care.
我爱我的祖国 我爱我的父母
I love my country, I love my mother, my father.
但是我最爱女人 对真主的爱也不及此
But I love cunt more than I love God!
她妈妈知道她在干什么吗?
Does her mama know that she's out?
大家认识这个人?
You know this man?
他是卡梅尔・汉纳
This is Kamel Hannah.
我父亲最好的朋友
He's my father's greatest friend.
他在吃东西
He tastes his food.
她向老师请假了吗?
Did she get a note from her teacher?
你看看这块表
See this watch?
看见没?
You see this watch?
你觉得这样的表值多少钱?
How much you think a watch like this costs?
多少? 这样的表多少钱? 一万美元
How much? How much you think a watch like this costs? $10,000.
一万美元的手表 我父亲买给他的
It's a $10,000 watch. My father bought him that watch.
为什么? 为什么我父亲要给卡梅尔・汉纳买这么个表
Why? Why did my father buy Kamel Hannah a watch like this?
要我告诉你吗? 要吗?
Shall I tell you why? Shall I tell you why?
要我说为什么我父亲如此喜欢 卡梅尔・汉纳吗?
Shall I tell you why my father loves Kamel Hannah so much?
- 因为卡梅尔为我父亲召妓 - 胡说
- Because he gets his whores for him. - Rubbish.
我们的母亲...她正在房间哭
Our mother...Our mother sits around the house and weeps
就是因为这个人为我父亲召妓
because of the whores this man brings my father.
我母亲在宫殿里来回徘徊
She wanders, she walks around the palace,
来回徘徊 然后站在镜子前
walks around the palace, staring in the mirrors,
盯着镜子 觉得自己看着像是该死的僵尸
staring in the mirrors, looking at herself like a fucking zombie
就是因为那些妓女 这个人给我父亲召的那些妓女
because of the whores this man brings my father!
- 我是不是该杀了他 兄弟? - 乌代
- Shall I kill him, brother? - Uday.
你觉得呢 兄弟?
What do you think, brother?
你觉得呢? 我该不该杀了他?
What do you think? Shall I kill him?
杀了我父亲最好的朋友?
Kill your father's greatest friend?
他这个胆小的拉皮条的 快把我母亲弄疯了
He is a twittering little pimp that has driven my mother mad.
- 也许我该让你帮我杀了他 - 乌代
- Maybe I'll let you kill him for me. - Uday.
不
No.
我不认识他 我没必要杀他
I don't know him. It's meaningless.
我要杀一个人 一定要有充分的理由
If I am going to kill somebody, I want to know why I'm going to do it.
乌代
Uday.
- 你个狗娘养的! - 别激动 别激动
- You fucker! - Easy, easy.
该觉得丢人的是你...
You should be ashamed of your...
狗娘养的
Motherfucker.
到我卧室来 来
Come into my bedroom. Come on.
要喝点什么吗? 很好喝的
Would you like a drink? A nice drink?
我喜欢威士忌
I like to drink whiskey.
拿着 给 给
Take it, here, here.
你要不? 要不要?
Would you like some? Would you like some?
就这样 一个鼻孔吸 一个 一个
That's it. In just one. In one. In one.
你太美了 你真是个美人儿
You're very beautiful. You're a very beautiful girl.
求我...求我上你
Beg me...Beg me to fuck you.
求我 快点 求我上你
Beg me. Go on, beg me to fuck you.
他羞辱我
He humiliate me.
怎么不说呢? 说吧 求我 求我上你
Why not? Just say it. Beg me. Bag me to fuck you.
- 我说不出 - 别这样
- I can't. - Come on.
- 我... - 然后?
- I... - Yes?
- ...求... - ...求...
- ...beg... - ...beg...
...你...不行 我说不出口
...you...I can't.
- 继续 - 不行
- Go on. - No.
- 快求我 快求我 - 不
- Beg me. Beg me. - No.
求我! 求我上你
Beg me! Bag me to fuck you.
求我上你
Beg me to fuck you.
求我上你! 求我!
Beg me to fuck you! Beg me!
- 求我! 快点求我! - 我求...
- Beg! Beg! Beg! - I beg...
亚瑟姆! 亚瑟姆!
Yassem! Yassem!
- 那是谁? - 卡梅尔・汉纳那头猪 他就是不住手
- Who's doing that? - That pig, Kamel Hannah. Ha won't stop.
他说他不听命于同性恋
He says he doesn't take orders from faggots.
住手!
Stop!
- 去你妈的 - 我命令你给我住手!
- Fuck you. - I order you to stop!
我不听从你的命令 我听从的是萨达姆・侯赛因的命令
I don't take orders from you! I take orders from Saddam Hussain.
乌代 乌代...
Uday, Uday...
不要! 不要!
No! No!
头儿 快点 我们走
Boss, come on. Let's go.
把她带走 明白不?
Just get her out of here, okay?
他吞安眠药了
He took pills, sleeping pills.
把刀给我
Give me the knife.
你这样会杀死他的
You'll kill him.
失血过多 还有...
The loss of blood and...
他一出生 我就该阉了他
I should have gelded him at birth.
今晚七点 全副武装的美军开始
At 7:00 tonight the armed forces of the United States began an operation
向总统府方向挺进
at the direction of the President
迫使萨达姆・侯赛因从科威特撤军
to force Saddam Hussein to withdraw his troops from Kuwait
并结束其对科威特的占领
and to end his occupation of their country.
这是最新的战斧巡航导弹
That's the latest Tomahawk cruise missile
刚从我们上方飞过
to fly just over our position here.
所有的防空高射炮都试图将它们击落
Anti-aircraft gunners all around have been trying to shoot them down.
我告诉过伊拉克人民
I have said to the people of Iraq
我们的争执不是针对他们
that our quarrel was not with them,
而是针对他们的领导人
but instead with their leadership
尤其是萨达姆・侯赛因
and above all with Saddam Hussein.
科威特一直在偷我们的石油
Kuwait has been stealing our oil.
致使我们每年损失几百万的美元
Millions of dollars a year.
几百万美元 几百万的美元
Millions of dollars. Millions of dollars.
科威特一直在偷我们的石油 我们每年损失几百万美元
Kuwait has been stealing our oil. Millions of dollars a year.
就是从这些油田中 从我们鲁迈达的油田中偷走的
From the oilfields. From our oilfields at Rumaila.
科威特
Kuwait.
科威特 科威特
Kuwait, Kuwait.
科威特偷走了我们伊拉克的石油!
Kuwait has stolen our Iraqi oil!
每年从我们鲁迈拉油田偷走几百万美元
Millions of dollars a year from our oilfields at Rumaila.
我们国家一年就损失超过十个亿!
Our country is losing more than a billion dollars a year!
把墨镜摘下来
Take the glasses off.
你来这做什么?
What are you doing here?
- 你怎么进来的? - 要我走?
- How did you get in? - Do you want me to go?
干嘛在凌晨一点戴着墨镜?
Why are you wearing Ray-Bans at 1:00 in the morning?
摘了它
Take them off.
- 我要确定这是你 - 确定了?
- I want to be sure it's you. - Are you sure'?
我看得出来
I can always tell.
你不能呆在这
You cannot stay here.
难道你不知道外面发生了什么吗?
Have you seen what's going on outside?
知道萨达姆在电视上都说了什么吗? 《战争之母》
Hear what Saddam said on television? "The mother of all battles"
伊拉克人民不是傻子 没人信那套
Iraqi people are not stupid. Nobody believes that crap.
伊拉克要被战火夷为平地了 我们可不会在电视上看到这个
Iraq is going to burn to the ground. We won't see that on TV.
乌代呢? 在汇报工作吗?
And Uday? Is he reporting for duty?
没 乌代睡了 头疼得厉害
No. Uday has gone to bed with a splitting headache
因为亚瑟姆・阿尔赫洛忘熨他的花呢狩猎马裤了
because Yassem AI-Helou forgot to press his tweed hunting breaches.
他还是个孩子 他会对你厌倦的
He's a child. He'll tire of you.
他厌倦任何事物
He tires of everything.
很快有一天 他会厌倦我的
One day soon, he'll tire of me
我会被丢到湖里喂鱼
and I'll end up at the bottom of the lake with the fish.
他现在还挺喜欢你的 相当欣赏你
Today he's infatuated with you. He's quite dazzled.
他觉得他造就了你 发掘了你
He thinks he made you up, just like that, out of the dust.
而明天他打个响指 你就消失了
Tomorrow he snaps his fingers and you vanish.
但你可以离开 萨拉布
But you can leave, Sarrab.
就算我跑了 他也会找到我的
If I run away, he'll find me.
如果找不到我 他会去找我妹妹
If he can't find me, he'll find my sister.
谁会保护我从乌代的眼皮下逃走? 你吗?
Who's going to protect me from Uday Hussein? You?
在伊拉克世道就是这样
This is the way it is in Iraq.
是他
It's him.
拉O夫?
Latif?
我睡不着
I cannot sleep.
吃点药吧
Take a pill.
现在你可以吻我了
You may kiss me now.
你必须去巴士拉 我的儿子
You must go to Basra, my son.
- 他说了什么? - 那不是他
- What did he say? - It's not him.
- 那当然是他 - 你连自己的亲生父亲都认不出来吗?
- Of course it's him. - You don't know your own father?
- 那不是他 - 我当然认得出 他说什么了?
- It wasn't him. - Of course I do. What did he say?
巴士拉
Basra.
巴士拉?
Basra?
去他的巴士拉
Fuck Basra.
甭指望我会去
Don't expect me to go.
科威特偷走了我们伊拉克的石油!
Kuwait has stolen our Iraqi oil!
每年从我们鲁迈拉油田偷走几百万美元
Millions of dollars a year from the oilfields at Rumaila!
我们国家一年就损失好几十个亿啊!
Our country is losing more than a billion dollars a year!
科威特算什么东西 是谁建立了这个国家?
What is Kuwait? Who made up this country?
是做贼的英国人
The thieving British!
在1935年 他们用笔在沙子上画了条线
In 1935 they picked up a pen and drew a line in the sand.
科威特只是个白日梦
Kuwait is a fantasy!
- 看啊 妈妈 是我 - 科威特是个谎言
- look, Mother. It's me. - Kuwait is a lie!
科威特是伊拉克的一个省
Kuwait is the province of Iraq!
酋长的时代已经结束了!
The age of the sheikhs is over!
- 库塞吗? - 乌代
- Qusay? - Uday.
- 你在看吗? - 他骗不过我 哥哥
- Are you watching? - He didn't fool me, my brother.
你可以区分的出? 哪里不一样?
You can tell? How?
首先 他人很清醒 其次 嘴里没有唾沫横飞
For one thing he's sober, and second he's not foaming at the mouth.
陷阱!
It's a hit!
- 我们走! - 快! 快! 快!
- Let's go! - Go! Go! Go!
你失了很多血
You've lost a lot of blood.
我们可能要切除这根小指
We might have to lose the little finger.
谁去告诉乌代?
Who's going to tell Uday?
再押点 再押点
Take more. Take more.
先生
Monsieur:
干嘛? 什么?
What? What?
小手指 右手的 他们正竭尽全力
The little finger. Right hand. They're doing their best.
操!
Fuck!
是你吗?
Is it you?
是我
It's me.
美国人说乌代被叶什派的人击毙了
The Americans are saying Uday has been shot by the Shi'a.
但我知道乌代在日内瓦 和他叔叔赌博呢
But I know Uday is in Geneva, gambling with his uncle.
他昨晚打电话给我了
He called me last night.
嗯 这是你
Yes, it is you.
- 拉蒂夫在哪? 手指受伤的拉蒂夫... - 我正忙着呢 病人快要死了
- Where's Latif? Latif, with the finger... - I'm busy. People are dying.
病人快要死了! 病人快要死了! 病人快他妈要死了!
People are dying! People are dying! People are fucking dying!
我知道病人快要死了! 我知道他们快要死了!
I know people are dying! I know they are dying!
男人 女人 伊拉克的士兵们 失去了手臂和他妈的腿 英勇的人们
Men, women, Iraqi soldiers losing arms and fucking legs. Brave people.
我他妈的才不管呢! 你明白吗?
I don't give a fuck! Do you understand me?
明不明白? 去他们的!
Do you understand me? Fuck them!
- 我他妈的才不管呢! - 你必须走了 现在
- I don't give a fuck! - You must go. Now.
快 快 快 快 走吧
GO, go, go, go. You must go.
保住他的手指
Save his finger.
要是保不住这个人的指头
If you fail to save this men's finger,
我就把这儿的所有人都杀了
I will kill every one of you.
我们打败了伊拉克的军队 我们实现了军事目标
Iraq's army is defeated. Our military objectives are met.
科威特回到了科威特人的手中
Kuwait is once more in the hands of Kuwaitis,
能够自己掌控命运
in control of their own destiny.
噢 我的天哪 看那儿
Oh, my God. Look at that.
我想干她 我真的想干她 你想干她不?
I could fuck that. I could really fuck that. Could you fuck that'?
亚瑟姆
Yassem.
我想知道她是不是处女
I wonder if she's a virgin.
你觉得她是个处女吗?
Do you think she's a virgin?
今天是她结婚的日子 是他一生中 最美好的一天 她是那个男人的新娘
It's her wedding day. It is the best day of her life. She is the man's bride.
你觉得她会让我把手指戳进她的屁股吗?
Do you think she'll let me stick my finger up her ass?
她会吗?
You think?
过来 来
Come over. Come on.
来
Come.
我喜欢这裙子
I do like that dress.
到这来 亲爱的
Come here, darling.
你很漂亮 非常 非常漂亮
You're beautiful, very, very beautiful.
今天开心吗? 来 让我亲你一下
You having a nice day? Come, let me kiss you.
非常好 兄弟
Very good. My brother.
没什么的 你看 我被杀的谣言
Nothing serious. As you can see, rumors of my death
- 都是无耻的谎言... - 是我
- are scandalous lies... - It's me.
...美国人编出来的
...put out by the Americans.
无耻地侮辱了伊拉克人民的智商
Scandalous lies that insult the intelligence of the Iraqi people.
真主伟大
Allahu akbar.
真主伟大?
Allahu akbar?
真主什么也没给我
Allah gives me nothing.
我想要什么尽管自己去拿就是了
Everything I want I just take for myself.
看看我
Look at me.
我是个牛逼的战争英雄
I'm a fucking war hero.
呃 她死了
Well, she's dead.
查查她是谁 给他们些钱 做赔偿 你聋了吗?
Find out who she is. Send them some dinars for the damage. Are you deaf?
我说打给奥林匹克委员会的赛德
I said pick up the phone, get hold of Said at the Olympic Committee.
- 照我说的做 - 你自己去!
- Do what I tell you. - Do it yourself!
什么? 你说什么?
What? What did you say?
我说你自己去 我不想掺合进这件疯狂的事情
I said do it yourself. I will not be part of this madness.
我永远不会放你走的 我永远也不会放你走的
I will never let you go. I will never let you go.
我太爱你了
I love you too much.
亚瑟姆
Yassem.
我应该一枪打爆他的脑袋
I should have put a bulletin his head.
那你就跟他一个样了
Then you would be just like him.
但你不是
And you're not.
感谢真主
Praise God for that.
你是我的拉蒂夫
You're my Latif.
- 你必须走 - 不 他走了 他走了
- You must go. - No, he's gone. He's gone.
我知道 但是他还会回来的 你必须走
I know, but he'll be back. You must go.
你怎么能忍受这一切? 为什么你要选择这样的生活?
How can you stand it'? Why do you choose to live like this?
我没得选
I didn't choose.
是他选择了我 就像他选择了你一样
He chose me, just like he chose you.
有个人要见你
You have a visitor.
我要你替我做点事
I want you to do something for me.
我会查一查这个投诉
I will look into this complaint.
有必要的话 我会告诉我父亲
If need be, I will talk to my father.
我非常疲倦
I'm a tired man.
我心脏不好
I have a heart condition.
看着我的眼睛 看深点
Look into my eyes. Look deep.
看得到里面的痛苦吗?
Can you see the pain there'?
这是你给伊拉克人民带来的痛苦
This is the pain you give to the people of Iraq.
永无止境的痛苦
Pain that never ends.
今天我来讨公道
Today I have come to seek justice.
我能得到一点怜悯吗?
Will I be shown any compassion?
公道 怜悯
Justice. Compassion.
去他妈的!
Fuck this!
是他吗?
Is this him?
你的女儿是个婊子 她喜欢那样
Your daughter was a whore. She enjoyed it.
她只有14岁 从来还没有任何男人碰过她
She was 14 years old. No man has ever touched her.
上帝赐予了她美貌 这就是她自甘堕落
God gave her beauty. This was her downfall.
太过分了 你是个罪犯
This is too much. You are a criminal.
- 整个伊拉克都知道你的罪行 - 你是个好人行了吧
- All of Iraq knows your crimes. - You are a good man.
给他一千块买他的女儿 这钱对于婊子来说是个好价钱
Give him 1,000 dinars for her time. That is good money for a whore.
干! 干! 干你娘的!
Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you!
我他妈的一枪崩了你的脑袋!
I'll put a fucking bullet in your fucking head!
你 你 现在朝他脑袋上开一枪 立刻!
You, you, put a bullet in his head now. Now!
- 他做了什么? - 他做了什么?
- What has he done? - What has he done?
- 他只是个失去了女儿的父亲 - 你没听见他是怎么说你的吗?
- He's a man who has lost his daughter. - You heard what he said about you?
- 说我? - 就是你 乌代・萨达姆・侯赛因
- About me? - About you, Uday Saddam Hussain.
又不是我把她从大街上抓走的
It was not me who snatched her off the street.
我没有打她 你想杀他的话 自己动手吧
I didn't beat her. If you want to kill him, kill him yourself.
由得你选吗? 由得你选吗?
You think you can pick and choose? You think you can pick and choose?
你什么都不是! 没有我 你应该被挂在
You are nothing! Without me, you'd be hanging
海法街的某个他妈的灯柱上
from a fucking lamppost on Haifa Street.
我造就了你 拉蒂夫 我造就了你 我给了你生命
I made you, Latif. I made you. I gave you life.
只要我愿意 我随时都可以拿走 现在朝他的脑袋开枪
If I want, I'll fucking take it away. Now put a bullet in his head.
我不会杀他的 想杀就杀我吧
I'm not going to kill this man. Kill me if you want.
- 我不管 - 你想以死救他?
- I don't care. - You would die to save this man?
来啊 你在等什么? 杀了我 朝我的脑袋开一枪
Go on, what are you waiting for'? Kill me. Put a bullet in my head.
反正总有一天当你情绪失控就会这么做的
You're going to do it one of these nights when the mood takes you.
干嘛不现在呢? 来啊 朝我的脑袋开一枪
Why not now? Go on, put a bullet in my head.
绝不 我太爱你了
Never. I love you too much.
不
No.
你爱的是乌代
You love Uday.
你不怕死是吧?
You are not afraid to die?
别忘了
You forget.
我在来这的那天就已经死了
I died the day I came here.
你不怕真主吗?
You do not fear God.
让你看看就这么简单
Let me make this easy for you.
我还不信了 来人把这拍下来
I don't believe it. Somebody get this on tape.
亚瑟姆! 过来拍
Yassem! Come film this.
- 这可比色情片精彩多了! - 给我接医院
- This is better than a porno movie! - Get me the hospital.
- 给我让开 - 亚瑟姆 拍下来 拍下来
- Get out of my way. - Yassem, film this. Film this.
亚瑟姆! 亚瑟姆!
Yassem! Yassem!
亚瑟姆!
Yassem!
找人帮忙
Get help.
我最不愿意和他约会
He's the last person I'd be going out with.
- 但他是我最好的朋友 - 那你去和他约会吧
- But he's my best friend. - Well, you go out with him, then.
- 和谁约会? - 没谁 爸爸
- Go out with who'? - Nobody, Baba.
我错过了什么吗?
Am I missing something here?
- 我去开门 - 是的 爸爸
- I'll get it. - Yes, Baba.
格拉哈下周就要结婚了
Gallalha's getting married next week.
她吗? 挺好的
Is she? That's good.
我的日子就轻松多了
Makes life much easier for me.
爸!
Baba!
是拉蒂夫
It's Latif!
朱安 去忙点别的吧 亲爱的
Ju'an, run along, habibi.
乌代・萨达姆・侯赛邀请你参加一个聚会
Uday Saddam Hussein invites you to a party.
他的生日宴会
His birthday.
他永远不会停手
He is never going to stop.
儿子
Son,
你做了什么我不想知道
I don't want to know what you've done
我想要你知道 我绝对信任你
I want you to know that I absolutely trust you.
并且我以你为傲
And I am proud of you.
将来 我们面对真主的时候
One day, when God wills it,
我们会得到公正的审判
we'll have justice.
你必须走
You must go.
必须离开这个国家 有多远走多远
You must leave this country, go as far away as you can,
别回来 除非乌代・侯赛因真的死了
and don't come back until Uday Hussein is dead and buried.
他会来找我的
He will come looking for me.
他会找到这来的 你知道的 他会来找你
He will come here. You know that. He will come looking for you.
去参加这个聚会吧 装装样子 我们要找准时机
Go to this party, drink his whiskey. We must look for the right moment.
- 别逼我了 - 拉蒂夫 我年纪大了
- Don't ask me to do this. - Latif, I am an old man.
我的生活在这里 我生活里所有的一切
My life is here. Everything I have made of my life.
真主给了我生命 儿子
God gave me life, my son.
当他要拿走的时候 他会拿走的
When he wills it, he'll take it away.
照我说的去做吧
You will do as you are told.
你
You.
你 你 穿蓝色裙子的 穿蓝色裙子的
You, you, in the blue dress. In the blue dress.
脱掉 脱掉 统统脱掉 脱吧 脱了 脱啊
Get it off. Get it off, all of it. Get it off, get it off, get it off.
继续 脱 脱 脱
Go on, take, take, take.
你们全部都 全部 你 穿金色衣服的
All of you, all of you. You, in the gold.
给我...脱了你的裙子 脱掉你的裙子!
Give me...Take off your dress. Take off your dress!
这是乌代给朋友们的生日宴会
It's Uday's birthday party for my friends
我想看到每个人的裸体 每一个人!
and I want to see all of you naked, all of you!
快点! 快! 脱光光 再脱 蓝色衣服的 衣服脱了!
Come on! Come on, naked. More. Blue clothing. Take it off!
现在 脱 所有衣服 脱了你的内裤
Now, off. All of it. Take your knickers off.
好漂亮的屁股啊 多漂亮啊
Beautiful ass. Beautiful ass.
快点! 脱了它! 这是生日狂欢
Come on! Take it off! This is birthday celebration!
好 真好 非常好 我喜欢
Good, good, good. I like it.
你 别藏着啊 让我看看
And you. Don't hide yourself. Let me see you.
你真美 真漂亮 你真应该秀一秀自己
You're beautiful. You're beautiful. You should show yourself.
这么多漂亮的人来我的生日聚会
It is a lot of beautiful people for my birthday.
- 那辆梅赛德斯... - 非卖品
- That Mercedes... - It's not for sale.
听说你要价三万
I heard you'd take 30,000.
有两件事我不干 赛德
There are two things I never do, Said.
我从不在总统面前放屁
I never pass wind in the presence of the President of the Republic
我也从来不和你这样的皮条客做买卖
and I never do business with pimps like you.
拉蒂夫! 拉蒂夫!
Latif! Latif!
伟大的真主啊
God is great.
他把我兄弟还给了我
He gives my brother back to me.
- 你不会吧? - 你说呢? 过来
- You didn't? - I did. Come.
来 来 来 来 来
Come, come, come, come, come.
我挺享受的
I quite enjoyed it.
真是疼得要命 我该去缝几针的
It hurt like hell. I thought I would need stitches.
萨拉布会怎么说?
What is Sarrab going to say?
萨拉布?
Sarrab?
萨拉布会怎么说?
What is Sarrab going to say?
你他妈的干嘛要管萨拉布会怎么说?
Why the fuck should you care what Sarrab is going to say'?
看看他 拉蒂夫认为自己和我长得很像
Look at him. Latif thinks because he looks like me,
穿的像我 睡我的床
he dresses like me, he sleeps in my bed,
他觉得自己可以像我一样干女人
he thinks he can fuck like me.
你觉得你可以上我的女人?
You think you can fuck my women?
他吃醋了
He's jealous.
他想亲自上你
He wants to fuck you himself.
你知道这个该死的库尔德人 跟我说了什么吗?
You know what this fucking Kurd said to me?
我出价三万买那辆梅赛德斯
I offered him 30,000 dinars for that Mercedes.
他说他不会把他卖给一个拉皮条的
He said he wouldn't sell it to a pimp.
皮条客? 你叫这位先生皮条客?
Pimp? You called this gentleman a pimp?
- 先生? - 他叫你拉皮条?
- Gentleman'? - He called you a pimp?
- 还是乌代的 - 乌代的拉皮条? 乌代的拉皮条?
- Uday's. - Uday's pimp? Uday's pimp?
- 你叫他乌代的拉皮条的? - 他在撒谎
- You called this man Uday's pimp? - He's lying.
他是我的朋友
This man is my friend.
他是这个国家最成功的生意人之一
He is one of this country's most successful businessmen.
生意人?
Businessman?
做什么生意的? 拉皮条吗?
What business is that? Cunt?
- 坐 - 我要走了
- Sit down. - I'm leaving.
- 坐下 - 你要走吗? 不走?
- Sit down. - Are you leaving? No?
那我走了
I am leaving.
坐下 我正和你说话呢
Sit down. I'm talking to you.
你想干什么 乌代?
What do you want from me, Uday?
你是我的 拉蒂夫 我说什么你做什么 坐下
You belong to me, Latif. You do as I say. Sit down.
你朝我后背开枪吧
You are going to have to shoot me in the back.
站住!
Stop!
站住! 我命令你站住!
Stop! I order you to stop!
你大爷的!
Fuck!
带我走吧
Take me with you.
你不能把我留在这里
You can't leave me here.
杀了他 他会杀了你的
Kill him. He'd kill you.
我不是乌代
I am not Uday.
快走
Come on.
钥匙
Keys.
奶奶个腿的!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
你放他走的
You let him go.
他有枪
He had a gun.
你也有枪啊
You had a gun.
被他抢走了
He took it.
靠
Fuck.
接下来怎么办?
Second thoughts?
我应该把你留在那的 那才是明智之举
I should've put you out back there. Would've been the smart thing to do.
- 乌代就会那么做 - 他不会
- That's what Uday would have done. - Not so smart.
乌代会先杀了我
Uday would have killed me first.
- 身上有钱吗? - 没
- Do you have any money? - No.
- 一点没有吗? - 我又不是妓女
- Nothing? - I'm not a prostitute.
糟透了
Too bad.
会骑吗?
Do you ride?
上面说什么了? 上面都说了些什么 穆饶?
Well, what does it say? What does it say, Munem?
乌代・萨达姆・侯赛因逃离了伊拉克
Uday Saddam Hussein has fled Iraq.
坐下
Sit down.
这个女人是谁?
Who is this woman?
他碰上的一个妓女
Some whore he met.
一点的时候乌代要上新闻
Uday will make an appearance on the news at 1:00.
媒体正在往这赶
They're on their way here now.
她脚上没穿鞋
She has no shoes on her feet.
总是会这样
This is what happens.
你给他们机会
You give people an opportunity,
提拔他们 让他们吃你的
lift them up, let them eat at your table,
还睡在你的床上
sleep in your bed.
然而这就是他们怎么报答你的
And this is how they repay you.
哪位?
Who is this?
我坐在这看着阿里干你的妹妹呢
I'm sitting here watching Ali fuck your sister up the ass.
我没跟你开玩笑 拉蒂夫
I'm not joking with you, Latif
回巴格达吧
Come back to Baghdad.
我们还能一起抽抽烟
We can smoke a pipe together.
找找乐子 开开车
Fuck some women, drive some cars.
别告诉我你需要时间考虑 别让我久等 兄弟
Don't tell me you need time to think. Don't keep me waiting, brother.
别逼我
Don't force my hand.
回来吧 拉蒂夫
Come back, Latif.
我想你了
I miss you.
我在这没什么人可以说说话
I've got no one here to talk to.
想想你的父母吧
Think of your mother and your father.
他怎么知道这里的号码?
How did he get this number?
我们刚刚踏进门啊
We just walked through the door.
乌代认识所有人
Uday knows everybody.
马耳他的这些人在巴格达有许多生意
These people in Malta have a lot of business in Baghdad.
我认识有一半的人在这儿有资产
Half the people I know have money here.
他们来这玩女人
They come to get their tits done.
我们必须离开这里 我们不能呆在这
We've got to get out of here. We cannot stay hare.
我们刚一进门他的电话就来了
We walk through the door and he's on the phone.
他不会放过我们的 我了解他 他是个疯子
He will never leave us alone. I know him, he's a fanatic.
他不会罢休的 你没在听我说话
He will never stop. You're not listening to me!
别对我大吼大叫
Stop shouting at me!
我有个孩子
I have a child.
是个小女孩
A little girl.
名叫塔拉
Tara.
没人知道 甚至乌代都不知道
Nobody knows this, not even Uday.
她跟我妹妹呆在萨马拉
She's with my sister in Samarra.
你得帮帮我
You have to help me.
你必须做点什么 拉蒂夫 她才三岁
You have to do something, Latif. She's three years old.
我不能把她留在伊拉克
I can't leave my daughter in Iraq.
你现在才跟我说?
You tell me this now?
我太害怕了
I was too frightened.
- 我不知道你会做什么 - 这太疯狂了
- I didn't know what you'd do. - This is insane.
你疯了
You are insane.
- 你到底是个怎样的女人? - 就这些了 我发誓
- What kind of a woman are you? - There's nothing else, wallahi, I swear it.
你想要我怎么做?
What do you expect me to do?
孩子的父亲是谁?
Who is the father?
和他说啊
Talk to him.
你知道这孩子的父亲是谁吗?
Do you even know who the father is?
你现在是在用乌代的口吻和我说话 我能感觉出来
Now that's Uday talking. I can hear it.
孩子的父亲死了
He's dead.
我和我妹妹通过电话
I spoke to my sister.
她认识一个人可以把塔拉带去阿曼 但他想要美元
She knows a man who can drive Tara to Amman. He wants US dollars.
是你
It was you.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
乌代怎么会知道我在哪? 没有别的解释了
How else did Uday know where I was? There is no other way.
你从来都不会说点好听的 是吗?
You never say anything nice, do you?
你从没夸过我漂亮
You never say I look pretty.
你从没问过我的感受
You never ask me how I'm feeling.
你从来没有说过你爱我
You never tell me you love me.
你和我在床上鱼水之欢的时候
When you make love to me,
你很温柔
you're tender.
只有那时候
Only then.
看着我 拉蒂夫
Look at me, Latif.
看着我
Look at me.
你看到了什么?
What do you see?
乌代的婊子吗?
Uday's whore?
- 那就是你眼里的我吗? - 我和接线员聊过了
- Is that what I am to you? - I spoke to the operator.
他给了我一张电话记录
He gave me a list of outgoing calls.
我并没有给伊拉克大使馆打过三个电话
I didn't call the Iraqi Embassy three times.
打给伊拉克奥林匹克委员会的也不是我
It wasn't me who called the Iraqi Olympic Committee.
我害怕了
I got scared.
我是给我妹妹打的电话
I was calling my sister.
- 我担心我的女儿 - 是你 萨拉布
- I was scared for my daughter. - It was you, Sarrab.
你
You.
你打给乌代 告诉他我在哪
You called Uday. You told him where I was.
是你
It was you.
想拿什么就拿吧 萨拉布
Take what you want, Sarrab.
宾馆房间里还有些钱
There is money in the hotel room.
我可怜的拉蒂夫
My poor Latif.
萨拉布怎么样了?
And how is Sarrab?
她是不是跟你说她女儿 和她妹妹住在一起?
Did she tell you about her daughter living with her sister'?
你相信她的话了吧
And you believed her.
先别挂电话 你个蠢货 你老爹在我这呢
Don't hang up the phone, motherfucker. I have your father in my office.
让我跟他说话
Let me speak to him.
回家吧 拉蒂夫
Come home, Latif.
替你爸爸想想
Think of your father.
回巴格达吧
Come back to Baghdad.
我把电话给你爸爸了
I'm going to put your father on the phone.
我想要你听听他会跟你说什么
I want you to listen to what he has to say to you.
他会告诉你该怎么做
He's going to tell you what to do.
给
Here.
跟你儿子说几句
Speak to your son.
你好吗 儿子?
Are you well, my son?
我很好 听着 我有个计划
Yes, I'm fine. Listen, I have a plan.
我只说一遍 这是我的遗言
I'm going to say this once, and it's my final word.
照我说的去做 否则你不再是我的儿子
You will do as I tell you or you are no longer my son.
告诉这个婊子养的人渣
Tell this evil son of a bitch
见鬼去吧
to goto hell.
说啊 拉蒂夫
Speak up, Latif.
你要说什么?
What is it to be?
见鬼去吧
Goto hell.
拉蒂夫・叶海亚
Latif Yahia.
那天早上他们把我父亲带到乌代的办公室
They took my father to Uday's office that morning.
下午四点他们丢弃了他的尸体
They dropped his body off at 4:00 in the afternoon.
他们禁止我母亲为他举办一个体面的葬礼
My mother was forbidden to give him a decent burial.
他们让她把父亲葬在花园里
She was told to bury him in the garden.
什么都无法挽回我妻子 和你父亲
Nothing will bring my wife back. Or your father.
你为什么来这?
Why have you come here?
你想怎么干?
What do you want?
嗨 美女! 美女!
Hey, girls! Girls!
你 过来跟我说句话呀
You, come and talk to me.
嗨 你 过来 来啊 我送你回家
Hey, you. Come here. Come. I'll take you home.
那个一头秀发的 你真是太漂亮了 别走 你是...
With the pretty hair. You're very pretty. No, you are...
拜托了 过来吧 你是哪儿人?
Please, come on. Where are you from?
想躲我啊 哈?
Trying to get away from me, huh?
他停下了
He's stopped.
来嘛 他们是你的朋友吗?
Come on. Are they your friends?
让开 阿里 阿里 亚瑟姆
Move. Ali. Ali, Yassem.
滚开! 滚开!
Get the fuck out! Move!
亚瑟姆! 亚瑟姆!
Yassem! Yassem!
阿里! 阿里! 不!
Ali! Ali! No!
- 不要! 亚瑟姆! 亚瑟姆! - 这是为了我妻子
- No! Yassem! Yassem! - This is for my wife!
拉蒂夫?
Latif?
不! 住手!
No! Please stop!
不! 不!
No! No!
闪开!
Out of my way!
让开!
Move!
你 站住!
You, stop!
让开 闪开!
Move, move!
站住!
Stop!
疏散人群!
Clear the area!
疏散!
让开!
Move!
拉蒂夫很难被找到 最后一次有人看到 他和他的妻子和两个孩子生活在爱尔兰
遇刺以后 乌代・侯赛因・萨达姆下身瘫痪 于2003年被美军击毙
其他请参见历史
谢谢观赏TLF字幕 TLF字幕组欢迎你:sub.eastgame.org